const nfpa211Chapter9QuizData = [
  {
    id: "9_1",
    question: "Connectors having under 6 inches (<6) in diameter should be what gauge? (NFPA 211 Table 9.2.2.3)",
    options: ["24 gauge", "26 gauge", "22 gauge", "16 gauge"],
    answer: "26 gauge"
  },
  {
    id: "9_2",
    question: "Connectors having 6 inches inclusive to 10 inches inclusive (>=6 to <=10) in diameter should be what gauge? (NFPA 211 Table 9.2.2.3)",
    options: ["24 gauge", "26 gauge", "22 gauge", "16 gauge"],
    answer: "24 gauge"
  },
  {
    id: "9_3",
    question: "Connectors having over 10 inches to 16 inches inclusive (>10 to <=16) in diameter should be what gauge? (NFPA 211 Table 9.2.2.3)",
    options: ["24 gauge", "26 gauge", "22 gauge", "16 gauge"],
    answer: "22 gauge"
  },
  {
    id: "9_4",
    question: "Connectors having over 16 inches (>16) in diameter should be what gauge? (NFPA 211 Table 9.2.2.3)",
    options: ["24 gauge", "26 gauge", "22 gauge", "16 gauge"],
    answer: "16 gauge"
  },
  {
    id: "9_5",
    question: "Connectors shall be as long as possible. (NFPA 211 9.3)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "9_6",
    question: "For a connector serving a solid fuel-burning appliance, the connector length shall be no more than _________ of the vertical height of the venting system. (NFPA 211 9.3.1)",
    options: ["75%", "50%", "25%", "100%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_7",
    question: "For a connector serving something other than a solid fuel-burning appliance, the connector length shall be no more than _________ of the vertical height of the venting system. (NFPA 211 9.3.1)",
    options: ["75%", "50%", "25%", "100%"],
    answer: "75%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_8",
    question: "The effective area of a connector for a single appliance shall be _________ the area of the appliance flue collar. (NFPA 211 9.4.2)",
    options: ["not less than", "not more than 50%", "not more than 25% less than", "not less than 50%"],
    answer: "not less than"
  },
  {
    id: "9_9",
    question: "A connector or manifold serving more than one appliance shall have an effective area equivalent to the combined areas of the appliance flue collars or individual connectors. (NFPA 211 9.4.3)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "9_10",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is a Gas appliance without a draft hood? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "18 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_11",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is an Electric, gas, or oil incinerator? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "18 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_12",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is an Oil and solid-fuel appliance? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "18 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_13",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is an Unlisted gas appliance with a draft hood? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "9 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_14",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is a Boiler or furnace equipped with listed gas burners and with draft hoods? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "9 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_15",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is an Oil appliance listed as suitable for use with Type L vents? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "9 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_16",
    question: "What is the default minimum clearance for Single-Wall Metal Pipe Connectors for a Residential-Type Appliance that is a Listed gas appliance with draft hoods or other Category I gas appliance listed for use with Type B vents? (NFPA 211 9.5.1.1)",
    options: ["6 inches", "9 inches", "18 inches", "36 inches"],
    answer: "6 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "9_17",
    question: "Wall protectors shall provide possibility of air circulation with at least a ________ air gap? (NFPA 211 9.5.5.1-3)",
    options: ["6 inch", "1 inch", "2 inch", "4 inch"],
    answer: "1 inch"
  },
  {
    id: "9_18",
    question: "If a thimble is not used, the connector itself shall be fastened via tapcons to masonry. (NFPA 211 9.7.1)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "9_19",
    question: "A chimney connector shall not pass through any floor, ceiling, fire wall, or fire partition. (NFPA 211 9.7.2)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "9_20",
    question: "Connectors shall maintain a pitch or rise of at least _________ of horizontal lenght of pipe from the appliance to the chimney. (NFPA 211 9.7.6)",
    options: ["1/4 inch per foot", "1/8 inch per foot", "1/2 inch per foot", "1 inch per foot"],
    answer: "1/4 inch per foot"
  },
  {
    id: "9_21",
    question: "A 3 1/2 inch thick masonry wall without ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "33%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_22",
    question: "1/2 inch thick noncombustible insulation board over 1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts without ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_23",
    question: "1/2 inch thick noncombustible insulation board over 1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts without ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a ceiling protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "33%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_24",
    question: "24 gauge sheet metal over 1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts reinforced with wire, or equivalent, on rear face with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "66%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_25",
    question: "24 gauge sheet metal over 1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts reinforced with wire, or equivalent, on rear face with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a ceiling protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_26",
    question: "3 1/2 inch thick masonry wall with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "66%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_27",
    question: "24 gauge sheet metal with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "66%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_28",
    question: "24 gauge sheet metal with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a ceiling protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_29",
    question: "1/2 inch thick noncombustible insulation board with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "66%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_30",
    question: "1/2 inch thick noncombustible insulation board with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a ceiling protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_31",
    question: "1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts sandwiched between 2 sheets of 24 gauge sheet metal with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a wall protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "66%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_32",
    question: "1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts sandwiched between 2 sheets of 24 gauge sheet metal with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a ceiling protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_33",
    question: "This isn't a question, just a heads up! The 'Minimum Clearance' columns on the connector reduction table (Table 9.5.1.2) are displaying numbers based on cases where the default unprotected clearance of 18 inches. This is stated in 9.5.1.2.1. However, 9.5.1.2.2 states to use Minimum Clearances from Table 9.5.1.1. According to the Connector Reduction Table, the formula to use would be  'Minimum Allowable Clearance = Minimum Clearance based on the Appliance/Connector from Table 9.5.1.1 * (100% - Reduction %)'. So for example, A regular Listed Gas Vent with Draft Hood, that doesn't have an appliance specifying anything different,reduced with one of the 66% options would have a Minimum Allowable Clearance of 2 inches. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["Understood!"],
    answer: "Understood!"
  },
  {
    id: "9_34",
    question: "Manually operated connector dampers shall not obstruct more than _________ of the connector area when closed. (NFPA 211 9.9.3)",
    options: ["80%", "95%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "80%"
  },
  {
    id: "9_35",
    question: "1 inch glass fiber or mineral wool batts sandwiched between 2 sheets of 24 gauge sheet metal with ventilated air space reduces clearance by _________ as a ceiling protector. (NFPA 211 Table 9.5.1.2)",
    options: ["33%", "50%", "66%", "75%"],
    answer: "50%"
  },
];

if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 9: Chimney Connectors and Vent Connectors'] = nfpa211Chapter9QuizData;

